Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at Sites of Public Works Projects in the United Arab Emirates
  - Two men interviewing H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000050_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Canes/Walking Sticks; Group Portraits; Men; Pens/Inkwells; Cigarettes; Smoking; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates
  - Three men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) about his public works projects outside the Abu Dhabi Telegraph and Telephone Company., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000051_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Street Lamps; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) with three men working on public works project plans in an office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000052_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Offices; Pens/Inkwells; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Clocks/Watches; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr on site of one of his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000053_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Buildings; Construction; Clocks/Watches; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair
  - Four men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) about his public works projects outside the Abu Dhabi Telegraph and Telephone Company., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000054_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Signs/Signposts; Flags; Mosques; Streets/Roads; Religious Sites; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Facial Hair; Officials; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Smoking; Cigarette cards
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) speaking to a group of men on site of one of his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000055_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Construction; United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches; Buildings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr sitting in a chair with his eyes closed., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000056_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Furnishings; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right, obscured) with two men in an office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000057_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.7 x 12.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Offices; Furnishings; Paintings; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Pens/Inkwells; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right, obscured) with two men in an office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000058_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.7 x 12.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Offices; Furnishings; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells; Clocks/Watches; Officials; Paintings; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan
  - Two men shaking hands in an office, with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in the background., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000059_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Paintings; Offices; Furnishings; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Clocks/Watches; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in an office with a bottle of Old Spice., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000060_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Offices; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; Clocks/Watches; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) reviewing public works plans in an office with four men., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000061_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Clocks/Watches; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Offices; Pens/Inkwells; Officials; Furnishings; Books; Paintings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with a man about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000062_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 17.7 x 12.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Safe; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Canes/Walking Sticks; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) talking with a man about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000063_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Canes/Walking Sticks; United Arab Emirates; Safe; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials
  - Four men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right) about his public works projects outside the Abu Dhabi Telegraph and Telephone Company., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000064_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Officials; Construction; Buildings; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches; Cigarettes; Smoking; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front, right) leading a tour of a public housing project., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000065_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Group Portraits; Men; Crowds; Streets/Roads; Construction; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Mountains/Hills; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Smoking; Cigarettes; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan (right) talking with four men in his office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000066_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Sheikhs; Officials; Offices; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; United Arab Emirates; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Drinks/Beverages
  - From the left: H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and an unidentified man in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000067_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Offices; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; United Arab Emirates; Sheikhs; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - Three men talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right) about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000068_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Officials; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Safe
  - From the left: H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000069_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Offices; Furnishings; Men; Group Portraits; Sheikhs; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - From the left: H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000070_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Offices; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells; Books; Jewelry; Officials; Sheikhs
  - From the left: H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000071_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Offices; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Pens/Inkwells; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Books; United Arab Emirates; Sheikhs; Officials; Clocks/Watches
  - From the left: H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000072_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; United Arab Emirates; Facial Hair; Offices; Officials; Sheikhs; Pens/Inkwells; Books; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Furnishings
  - From the left: H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000073_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Offices; Furnishings; Sheikhs; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Pens/Inkwells; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Books
  - From the left: H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000074_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Furnishings; Offices; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Men; Group Portraits; Sheikhs; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells; Books; Facial Hair
  - From the left: H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000075_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Books; Furnishings; Sheikhs; Officials; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Offices; Pens/Inkwells; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; United Arab Emirates
  - From the left: H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and four other men reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000076_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Books; Pens/Inkwells; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Furnishings; Offices; United Arab Emirates; Sheikhs; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) greeting an unidentified man., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000077_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Palm Trees; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Hats
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle) working on a public works project with his team., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000078_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Offices; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; United Arab Emirates; Books; Clocks/Watches; Pens/Inkwells; Facial Hair
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) talking with a group of people about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000079_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Buildings; Clocks/Watches; Books; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; United Arab Emirates; Officials
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr sitting in a chair with his eyes closed., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000080_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Offices; Furnishings; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with a man about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000081_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Construction; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) being interviewed by three men about his public works projects outside the Abu Dhabi Telegraph and Telephone Company., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000082_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Officials; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Microphones; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Smoking; Cigarettes; Cars/Trucks; Transportation
  - An automobile parked outside the Ministry of Labor's office in Ras Al Khaimah., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000083_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cars/Trucks; Ras Al-Khaimah, United Arab Emirates; Transportation; Offices; Arabic Calligraphy; Signs/Signposts; Electricity
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (middle, wearing kandoora) with a group of interviewers at one of the public works projects he oversaw., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000084_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Furnishings; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Electricity; Hats; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - A group of men touring a public housing project., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000085_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair; Clocks/Watches; Cigarettes; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with a man about his public works projects., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000086_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Officials; United Arab Emirates; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Canes/Walking Sticks
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second on the left) reviewing public works projects in an office with four men., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000087_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Offices; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Pens/Inkwells; Books; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Paintings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; United Arab Emirates
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr at a desk in an office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000088_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.9 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Telephones; Head Covers/Veils; Offices; United Arab Emirates; Officials; Furnishings
  - H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan (right) in his office, with two men next to his desk., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000089_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Officials; Sheikhs; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Books; Offices; Telephones; United Arab Emirates
  - From the front row, left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, and H.H. Sheikh Saif Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan reporting on their work at the Federal National Council., 1973; AD_MC_093_ref9_000090_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Microphones; Sheikhs; United Arab Emirates; Drinks/Beverages; Facial Hair; Government; Gatherings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) and H.E. Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan (left) reviewing public works plans in Sheikh Hamdan's office., Circa 1974-1979; AD_MC_093_ref9_000091_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Offices; Furnishings; Sheikhs; Officials; Facial Hair; United Arab Emirates; Pens/Inkwells; Clocks/Watches
- Official Portraits of H.E. Sheikh Rashid Bin Saeed Al Maktoum, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and Mona Al Otaiba, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and H.H. Sheikh Rashid Bin Saeed Al Maktoum in a crowd of people., Circa 1971-1972; AD_MC_093_ref10_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Crowds; Men; Officials; Sheikhs; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Rashid Bin Saeed Al Maktoum, H.E. Mana Al Otaiba, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1971-1972; AD_MC_093_ref10_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.3 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Sheikhs; Officials; Gatherings; United Arab Emirates
  - H.H. Sheikh Rashid Bin Saeed Al Maktoum (left) talking with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right)., Circa 1971-1972; AD_MC_093_ref10_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 20.3 x 26.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; United Arab Emirates; Sheikhs; Officials; Gatherings
- H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan's Visit to the United Kingdom
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front left), H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and Sheikh Sultan bin Suroor Al Dhaheri (middle back) in an airplane on their way to the United Kingdom., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref11_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 20.5 x 25.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Airplanes; Transportation; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Officials; Sheikhs; Royalty; Presidents; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; London, England, UK; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan upon arrival to the United Kingdom., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref11_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 20.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Officials; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; London, England, UK; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan with an unidentified man in an airplane on the way to the United Kingdom., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref11_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 20.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Airplanes; Transportation; London, England, UK; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Officials; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting British officials upon their arrival to the United Kingdom., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref11_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 20.5 x 25.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Officials; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; London, England, UK; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Group Portraits
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left of Sheikh Zayed), and Sheikh Sultan bin Suroor Al Dhaheri (right of Sheikh Zayed) touring the British Aircraft Corporation., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref11_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 20.5 x 25.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Airplanes; Transportation; Factories; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Sheikhs; Presidents; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; London, England, UK; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Machines; Signs/Signposts; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Group Portraits
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (behind Sheikh Zayed) touring the British Aircraft Corporation., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref11_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 20.5 x 25.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; London, England, UK; Factories; Airplanes; Transportation; Officials; Sheikhs; Presidents; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Machines
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (behind Sheikh Zayed) touring the British Aircraft Corporation., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref11_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 20.5 x 25.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)